( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
You had clearly lost your mind,
how could you interrupt the ritual?
This is impossible.
Sometimes,
pain can keep a person awake.
Normally,
I'm actually terrified of pain.
Regardless,
the Main Gate has opened.
What you've done
only delays the Celestial Realm's return.
When the Celestial Realm returns,
you
will still die.
The Celestials' arrival?
I'm quite looking forward to it too.
From now on,
the sea is boundless for fish to leap,
and the sky is high for...
you.
He just opened an immortal gate.
I wonder if inside him,
a Celestial Seed will form.
I'm just going out for some air
and to get familiar with the area.
Do you believe me?
I do.
I know you don't believe me.
Have you had dinner?
No.
Perfect.
You need an empty stomach before surgery.
Surgery?
Lie flat.
Step one, sterilize.
Step two,
get straight to it.
Am I going to die?
I'm a doctor,
not a killer.
The anesthetic has expired.
Sorry.
Just bear with it.
Got anything bigger?
Let me do it.
No Celestial Seed.
Why is your face so pale?
I forgot to stitch you up.
All done.
It might be a bit ugly,
but it's very sturdy.
Sleeping outside again?
I told you you'd catch a cold.
Why'd he use so much thread on the stitches?
Signs of infection are already showing.
Honestly,
how does he forget to sterilize every time?
The fever's gone.
Another beautiful day.
And I'm still alive.
Wonderful.
What is that?
Look, look!
Quick, look! A celestial!
Come, come.
Am I seeing this right?
Today I become an immortal!
Chenxiang opens the mountain!
From this day on,
no one can bully me.
No one at all.
I am
The Blessed One of Chenxiang.
Quick, look!
What does "Blessed One" mean?
How to cultivate immortality?
Huge reward for any info on the Blessed One.
We should be able to find the Celestial Seed now.
Am I...
Am I still alive?
No.
This place is hell.
I have to...
escape this madman's clutches.
Don't be afraid.
Very soon.
Welcome back, Immortal One.
Why hasn't the Celestial Realm returned?
What could have gone wrong?
May I ask, Heavenly Immortal,
why is this happening?
The Main Gate... it hasn't opened.
Su Yang, push the gate.
Let us out!
Here we go again.
Whatever you want,
we can handle it once we awaken.
Let us out!
We can save your Tongtong, and also...
Shut up.
The harder you kick,
the more you'll hurt yourself.
We share a symbiotic bond.
Stop this foolish behavior!
Symbiotic?
So that means,
if I die,
you'll die too.
Well, you should've said so sooner!
Are you insane? You'll die like this!
Do you really think
I'm afraid of dying?
May I ask the Holy Immortal's name?
This Immortal
is Zi Shu.
Of the twelve zodiac signs,
Zi Shu.
Welcome to the mortal realm, Immortal One.
What's your name?
This humble Immortal Emissary is Wang Qiusheng.
Immortal Emissary?
Immortal Servant would be more fitting.
What is your current strength?
As long as we don't cross the authorities,
within this city of Shanhai,
there's little we can't accomplish.
We were able to recruit members before
because ancient texts recorded
that the Immortal One could grant those without celestial fate
a chance to step onto the immortal path.
That's why they were so willing.
We hope the Immortal One
could display a divine miracle.
Please grant us your blessing.
Work hard,
and you'll naturally enter the immortal gate.
From this moment on,
hunt down one person with everything you've got.
Shanhai City...
Su Yang.
Stop! Stop!
As long as you stop,
whatever you want, we can negotiate.
That's right.
We promise we won't start any more trouble.
Stop! Stop!
As long as you stop,
whatever you want, we can negotiate.
That's right.
We promise we won't start any trouble.
I want all of you,
from this day forward,
to obey me.
Got it?
Yes, we agree.
We'll all obey you.
Very good.
I really look forward to our next meeting.
Perhaps
to become a gang boss,
I'll always lack a bit of courage.
Just now,
why didn't you kill me?
I didn't dare.
If you killed me,
I'd actually thank you.
Even if I killed you,
I still couldn't leave Black Street.
In your eyes,
what color is the sky?
Blue.
And the clouds?
White.
But in my eyes,
all of it...
is black.
Pitch black.
You're hungry.
Right, you must be hungry.
There are a few cups of instant noodles in the kitchen,
on the cabinet.
If they haven't expired.
You know, pain is a funny thing.
Sometimes it stimulates your mind.
But once you overcome it,
you stop being afraid.
Instead,
you start to enjoy it a little.
What a madman.
It seems they're
getting a bit impatient.